Sarnaut... That's what Sarnaut's prison looks like. Yes, I see the Creator's hand in everything.
Forgotten friend, you have sacrificed so much for us all.
Mother...
My daughter. You called, and I'm here.
I didn't think you'd answer... Because I...
I had to come. You were dead, and you came back. You were lost and you were found.
We will always be together now.
Yes! You've always forgiven her anything.
But ENOUGH!
You have no place in Sarn's world! Go away! You will not defile it!
But this is my world!
And when you enter it, you obey my laws.
This is the finale of the Play!
Sarnaut is the prison world for the god of Light, and now you will suffer the same fate he did!
Noooo! No, no, no... You will never get what you want!